https://www.instant-mex-auto-insur.com/wp/privacy-policy

800 345-4701
223 Via De San Ysidro,
San Ysidro, CA
Privacy Policy
Instant Mexico Auto Insurance   •  Privacy Policy Our commitment to privacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The information we collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information (etc.)The way we use information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order..We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.Our commitment to data securityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How to contact usShould you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at instant1@pacbell.net.“Instant” Mexico Auto Insurance Since 1973 we have been your ONE-STOP CENTER for all of your travel needs. Have any questions? Call us at (800)345-4701 or (619)428-4714
Scroll to top
